#### Your Cookies, Your Choice.

We use cookies and similar technologies that are necessary to run our Websites (essential cookies). We use Analytics, Functionality and Advertising/Targeting cookies to analyze our Websites traffic, optimize your experience, personalize content and serve targeted advertisement. You can switch off cookies at any time by visiting the Manage cookies option.

Accept All Cookies Accept Only Essential Cookies Customize Cookies

Search

English

Sign Up &Get 200 GoldLogin

Menu

Games

Tags

Faves

Support

Other

Close

English

Content Preferences

Please sign in to customize your preferences. Login or Create a Free Account

Filter games by content type:

 Female + Male Female + Female  Male + Male  Transgender

* Trending Genres
* Trending Tags

Click the heart to favorite a game

Favorited games will appear here

Manage your favorites on your profile page

Select your favorite game and start playing now!

* For more support or to provide feedback please see our Discord

* Hang out with us:

Privacy Notice
==============

**_Last Modified: February 26, 2024_**

**Introduction**

Nutaku.Net and Nutaku.Com are websites operated by NUTAKU ENTERTAINMENT LTD, a limited liability company organized under the laws of the Republic of Cyprus, having its head office at 195-197 Old Nicosia-Limassol Road, Block 1 Dali Industrial Zone, Cyprus 2540 (“Nutaku”). Nutaku and its representatives, officers, shareholders, subsidiaries, affiliates, parents, employees, and agents (collectively “**we**”, or “**us**” or “**our**”)) provide games (“Game(s)”) on the [Nutaku.com](https://www.nutaku.com/) and [Nutaku.net](https://www.nutaku.net/) websites (“Websites”) and on its associated properties, games and platforms (Games and Websites are hereinafter collectively referred to as “Website(s)”).

AYLO Billing Limited and AYLO Billing US Corp, are the companies processing transactions of users purchasing Nutaku Gold on Nutaku.

Please read this Privacy Notice carefully, as your access to and use of our Website signifies that you have read, understand, and agree to all terms within this Privacy Notice. If you do not agree with any part of this Privacy Notice or our terms, please do not access or continue to use our Website or otherwise submit your personal data. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal data.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please see “Contact Information” below for information on how to contact us.

### 1\. Scope

For the purposes of this Privacy Notice, “process”, “processed” or “processing” means any operation or set of operations performed on personal data or on sets of personal data (excluding disclosure thereof), whether by automated means, including one or several of the following operations: collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure, or destruction. Information on disclosure of personal data or of sets of personal data may be found in the “Disclosure of Your Personal Information” section below.

This Privacy Notice applies to information we collect:

* on this Website,
* in e-mail, text and other communications between you and this Website,
* through mobile applications you download from this Website, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and this Website, or
* when you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services if those applications or advertising include links to this Privacy Notice.

It does not apply to information collected by:

* us on any other website operated by us; or
* any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on this Website. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements.

### 2\. The Data We Process About You

Personal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified by (“**Personal****Information**”). It does not include data that has been anonymized or pseudonymized.

We may process different kinds of personal data about you, depending on whether you chose to create an account with us.

Persons who visit the Website without logging in or registering (“**Unregistered Users**”):

* Website activity data: We process information about how you use the Websites, products and services and interact with content and advertisements, including the pages you visit and search history on the Website, and the referring web page from which you arrived on the Websites. We process browser and operating system information, devices you use to access the Websites and your time zone setting. We also process online identifiers. Specifically, we process internet protocol (IP) address information and we set cookies as explained below in the section on Cookies and Automatic Data Processing Technologies.
* Identifiers: Some users may be asked to provide identifiers (including government-issued photo identification as well as other documentation) to verify that they are over the age of majority required to have access to the Website and to view their contents. In such cases, this information is processed by trusted third party age verification service providers and none of the information submitted is transmitted to us. This Privacy Notice does not apply to the privacy practices of these third-party age verification service providers. Read the privacy terms and conditions of these third-party service providers carefully.
* Online Forms and Communication Data**:** We process Contact Data and other information that you submit through online forms provided on the Website or information send to us via email, online support chats or such as information provided in the context of support requests or any other inquiries, the content reporting and moderation of content, and our internal complaint handling system.  

For persons who choose to create an account on the Website (“Registered Users”), we process the same categories of information described above for Unregistered Users, and additionally the following information:

* _Contact Data_ includes first and last name, billing address, email address, telephone number.
* _Profile Data_ includes your username and password, country, gender, purchases or orders made by you, your interests, preferences, feedback, and survey responses.
* _Transaction Data_ includes bank account and payment card details, details about payments to and from you and other details of products and services you have purchased or received from us.
* _Technical Data_ includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this Website.
* _Marketing and Communications Data_ includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.

We may process your data to produce and share aggregated insights that do not directly or indirectly identify you and are not associated with you. Such aggregate information is not personal information

### 3\. The Sources from Which We Process Personal Information

We use different methods to collect data from and about you including through:

* _Direct interactions_. Information that you provide when carrying out search queries on our Website or by filling in forms on our Website, in particular at the time of registering to use our Website, subscribing to our service, using the chat box to communicate with us, taking part in surveys, entering a contest or promotion sponsored by us, when reporting a problem with our Website. or requesting further services.
* _Automated technologies or interactions_. As explained in the section below on Cookies and Automatic Data Processing Technologies, we set cookies and other automatic techniques to process website activity data when you visit the Website.
* _Third parties_. We may receive personal data about you from various third parties, for example, other websites controlled by us or members of our corporate group, our business partners or other third parties.

### 4\. Purposes for Which We Use Your Personal Information

In general, we use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us for the following purposes:

* _Provision of services_: to present our Website and its contents to you, including any interactive features on our Website, and to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us; we also collect and use Personal Information to verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes;
* _Customer management(Registered Users Only)_: to manage a registered users’ account, to provide customer support via chat boxes and toll-free phone communication and notices to the registered user about their account and purchases, and notices about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide through it;
* _Customization of content_: to perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our Website content, products, or services, in order to develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our Website and other websites;
* _Advertising_: to communicate with you about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, our affiliates or other third parties (For more information, see “Choices About How We Collect, Use and Disclose Your Personal Information”);
* _Analytics_: to determine whether users of this Website are unique, or whether the same user is using this Website on multiple occasions, and to monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, demographic patterns;
* _Functionality and security_: to diagnose or fix technology problems, and to detect, prevent, and respond to actual or potential fraud, illegal activities, or intellectual property infringement;
* _Platform Safety:_ To promote safety and security on the Websites. We use the information we collect to help protect users from harm and provide safe, secure product.
* _Compliance_: to enforce our terms and conditions and to comply with our legal obligations;
* _Information you provide_: We will process Contact Data and user submitted personal information in any other way we may describe when you provide the information or for any other purpose with your consent provided separately from this Privacy Notice. 

**5\. Our Legal Bases under Canadian and European Union (EU) Privacy Law**

To the extent required by applicable law, we rely on several lawful bases to use your data in these ways. This means we process your personal data only where:

* You provide your consent to do so for a specific purpose: for example, when you allow us to show you personalized ads or to send you e-mail marketing.
* Biometric information is also processed by a third-party service provider based on your consent. You may withdraw your consent at any time. Read the privacy terms and conditions of these third-party service providers carefully.
* It is necessary to perform our contractual obligations as per our terms and conditions: for example, to create your account.
* It is necessary to comply with legal obligations: for example, we may be required to collect, use, or disclose your information in connection with civil, criminal, corporate, taxation, regulatory matters, or litigation.
* It satisfies a legitimate interest which is not overridden by your data protection interests: for example, to keep the Websites safe and secure from fraud and illegal activities.
* It is used to protect your or others’ vital interests: for example, in case of emergency or to prevent a crime or fraud.
* It is used for tasks carried out in the public interest: for example, to combat unlawful behaviour where it is in the public interest to do so and where the public interest is laid down by applicable law.

Depending on the circumstances, we may rely on different legal bases when processing your same information for different purposes. If you reside outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”), Switzerland or the United Kingdom (“UK”), the legal bases on which we rely may differ from those listed above.

### 6\. Disclosure of Your Personal Information

We do not disclose your Personal Information except in the limited circumstances described here:

* _Corporate Group_. We may disclose your Personal Information to members of our corporate group (that is, entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with us) to the extent this is necessary for the purposes of provision of services, customer management, customization of content, advertising, analytics, verifications, functionality and security, and compliance.
* _Service Providers_. To our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include processing credit card payments, risk and fraud detection and mitigation, providing customer service, performing business and sales analysis, customization of content, analytics, security, supporting our Website functionality, age verification, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our Website. These service providers may have access to Personal Information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes. Where required under applicable laws, we entered into data processing agreements with such service providers to ensure that personal information is only processed securely within our instructions.
* _Legal Successors_. To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us about our Website users is among the assets transferred. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to ensure that the entity to which we transfer your personal information uses it in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice.
* To comply with the law or protect our rights or the rights of third parties: We access, preserve and share your Personal Information with regulators, law enforcement or others where we reasonably believe such disclosure is needed to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request, (b) enforce applicable terms of use, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address illegal or suspected illegal activities, security or technical issues, (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; or € to maintain and protect the security and integrity of our Website or infrastructure. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us, in our sole discretion.

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. We also may share aggregated information with third parties for conducting general business analysis. This information does not contain any Personal Information and may be used to develop content and services that we hope you and other users will find of interest.

For more information on recipients of personal information, please see the section “Contact Information” below on how to contact us.

### 7\. Information Collected Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including information such as your internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, location, your mobile carrier, device information (including device and application IDs), search terms, and cookie information.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

* **Cookies (or browser cookies)**

Cookies are small text files that are stored in your web browser or downloaded to your device when you visit a website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognizes that cookie, and allow a website to recognize a user’s device.

We currently use the following types of cookies:

* * _Strictly necessary cookies_: These are cookies that are required for the operation of our Website. These include, for example, cookies that enable a user to log in to our Website and to check if a user is allowed access to a particular service or content.
    * _Analytical cookies_: These cookies allow us to recognize and count the number of users and to see how users use and explore our Website. These cookies help us to improve our Website, for example by ensuring that all users are able to find what they are looking for easily.
    * _Functionality cookies_: These cookies are not essential but help us to personalize and enhance your online experience on our Website. This type of cookies allows us to recognize you when you return to our Website and to remember, for example, your choice of language.
    * _Targeting cookies_: These cookies record the visit of a user on our Website, the pages a user has visited and the links a user has followed in order to enable us to make our Website more relevant to the users' interests.

Analytics, Functionality and Advertising/Targeting cookies can be switched off at any time by accessing the ‘Manage cookies’ option that is located at the footer of The Website. However, if you decline to accept these cookies, some functionality on The Website may be disabled and can interrupt your access to certain parts of The Website.

Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires automatically when you close your browser. A persistent cookie will remain until it expires, or you delete your cookies. Expiration dates are set in the cookies themselves; some may expire after a few minutes while others may expire after multiple years.

Do Not Track: Our systems do not recognize browser “Do Not Track” signals.

_Flash Cookies_. Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see “**Choices About How We Collect, Use and Disclose Your Personal Information**”.

* **Web Beacons:**

Pages of our Website and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags, single-pixel gifs and web bugs) that are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies, which are stored on the user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on the web pages (or in an email) and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages or opened an e-mail, to understand usage patterns and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). We also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website.

* **Analytics:**

We use third party analytics and advertising tools and technologies, in particular Google Analytics and DoubleClick provided by Google, Inc., USA (“Google”). These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including IP addresses, devices, and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior and usage information, feature use metrics and statistics, usage and purchase history, media access control address (MAC Address), mobile unique device identifiers, and other similar information via the use of cookies. The information generated by Google Analytics and DoubleClick about your use of this Website (including your IP address) may be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Because we activated IP anonymization for Google Analytics and Double Click, Google will anonymize the last octet of a particular IP address. Only in exceptional cases, the full IP address is sent to and shortened by Google servers in the USA. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of this Website, compiling reports on Website activity, and managing advertising content. The information collected by Google Analytics may be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States pursuant to standard contractual clauses approved by the EU and the adequacy decision of the EU Commission C (2023) 4745 confirming an adequate level of data protection in the US under the EU-US Data Privacy Framework and applicable national extensions (for example the UK Extension to the EU-US Data Privacy Framework). You can learn more on how Google uses data [here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites), and you can opt-out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) or by accepting only necessary cookies.

### 8\. Third-party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on this Website are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Website. Unless expressly stated otherwise, our website does not provide any Personal Information to these third parties, however the information they collect may be associated with your Personal Information or they may collect information, including Personal Information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see “**Choices About How We Collect, Use and Disclose Your Personal Information**”.

### 9\. Choices About How We Collect, Use and Disclose Your Personal Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the Personal Information you provide to us.

* You can choose not to provide us with certain Personal Information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our Website because such information may be required in order for you to register as a member; purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions on our Website.
* You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this Website may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
* You may opt out of the double-click a cookie or of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](https://adssettings.google.com/anonymous?hl=en) or by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available at [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).
* You can opt out of receiving marketing emails from us using the opt-out link provided in our emails or by changing your preferences in your account settings if you are a Registered User, we may also continue to send you other types of important emails e.g., e-mails about your account.
* You may opt out of interest-based advertising on mobile devices by activating the “Limit Ad Tracking” or equivalent feature offered by your mobile platform. It will transmit a signal to us and to third parties that indicates your data should not be used for interest-based advertising.
* You may also delete and deactivate your account with us at any time unless we are required not to do so by law or by a court order. If you do so, your profile will no longer be accessible by you. If you later choose to have an account with us, you will have to sign up for a new account as none of the information you previously provided or saved within your account will have been saved.

### 10\. California Consumer Privacy Act Notice

As of January 1, 2020, the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) provides California residents (“Consumer(s)”) certain rights with respect to their personal information, as this term is defined under the CCPA. In addition to the rights that we state under this Privacy Notice, and subject to the exceptions found under the CCPA, Consumers have the right to: 

* Limit the use and disclosure of their personal information;
* Opt-out of the sale of their personal information, should we sell their personal information; 
* Be informed of certain information concerning our collection and use of their personal information; 
* Request that we delete certain personal information we collected from them; 
* Not be subjected to discrimination for the exercise of these rights. We will not deny California residents the use of our service, neither will we provide a different level or quality or services for exercising any of their CCPA rights, unless as permitted under the CCPA. 
* Correct inaccurate personal information that we have about them.

The Website does not sell, nor has it sold in the past twelve (12) months personal information to third parties for monetary or other valuable consideration. We may however disclose certain personal information with third parties, service providers and entities within our corporate group to enable them to perform certain services on our behalf, and namely to make the Website function properly, as further described in the section above titled _Disclosure of Your Personal Information_.  

To exercise the rights described above, please use the buttons at the bottom of this page or email us at [support@nutaku.net](mailto:support@nutaku.net) with the email subject line “CCPA Request.” In either case you will need to provide the following information to verify your identity and enable us to locate your information in our systems: your username and email address that you used to create an account with us, as well as any other information which we may reasonably request for us to verify your identity. We may require you verify that you have access to your account and/or email account that you used to register with us.

You can designate an agent to make a request by executing a notarized power of attorney to have that person act on your behalf and providing that person with the information listed above that allows us to verify your identity and locate your information. Alternatively, you will need to directly confirm your identity with us using the methods described above, sign an authorization for the agent to act on your behalf and provide us with confirmation that you have done so.

### Resident’s Rights – Jurisdictions in the United States, Where Applicable

We do not sell, trade, or exchange the Registered Users’ personal information with anyone for money.

**11\. Biometrics**

We employ third-party service providers to help verify your identity and the authenticity of identification documents you provide using facial recognition technology when required.

Facial recognition technology creates a mathematical representation of your facial features from the live scan of your face, your selfie, and the government-issued ID you submit or previously submitted to us. Information derived from this mathematical representation, which may be considered biometric information under the laws of certain states and countries, is shared by our service providers with us as further described below.  

Your biometric information will be processed to: 

* verify you are a real-life person and to prevent the use of methods which would allow a user to identify as someone else; 
* to help confirm your age

We only process biometric information in jurisdictions that require age verification to access the Websites. Such verification is processed through a trusted third party provider.

### 12\. Financial Information

Financial information (including Personal Information) that you have provided to us will only be shared with our third-party processors in order to initiate and complete any orders placed on your account. All credit card transactions and such are processed with industry standard encryption through third party processors who only use your financial information and Personal Information for that purpose. All financial data and related Personal Information will not be shared by us with third parties except with your authorization or when necessary to carry out all and any transactions requested by you with the understanding that such transactions may be subject to rules, terms, conditions, and policies of a third party. All such information provided to a third party is subject to their terms and conditions.

### 13\. Transfers of Your Personal Information to Other Countries

Whenever in the course of sharing information we transfer Personal Information to countries outside of the European Economic Area (EEA) and other regions with comprehensive data protection laws, we will ensure that the information is transferred in accordance with this Privacy Notice and as permitted by the applicable laws on data protection.

By using this Website, you consent to the transfer of information that we collect about you, including personal information, to any country in which we, members of our corporate group (that is, entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with us) or our service providers are located.

### 14\. Retention of Personal Information

We will only retain your Personal Data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

Where we no longer need to process your Personal Data for the purposes set out in this Privacy Notice, we will delete your Personal Information from our systems.

Where permissible, we will also delete your Personal Data upon your request. Information on how to make a deletion request can be found under “**Your Rights Related to Your Personal Information**”.

If you have questions about our data retention practices, please send us an e-mail at [support@nutaku.net](mailto:support@nutaku.net).

The period for which we keep your Personal Information that is necessary for compliance and legal enforcement purposes varies and depend on the nature of our legal obligations and claims in the individual case.

### 15\. How We Protect the Security of Your Personal Information

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic, and procedural measures) to safeguard your Personal Information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access Personal Information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption in the transmission of your Personal Information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your Personal Information. Please be advised, however, that we cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with the storage and transmission of Personal Information.

You are responsible for always maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information. We are not responsible for circumventions of any privacy settings or security measures contained on this Website.

### 16\. Your Rights Related to Your Personal Information

Subject to local law, you have certain rights regarding the Personal Information we collect, use or disclose and that is related to you, including the right:

* to receive information on the Personal Information concerning we hold about you and how such Personal Information is used (right to access);
* to rectify inaccurate Personal Information concerning you (right to data rectification);
* to delete/erase your Personal Information (right to erasure/deletion, “right to be forgotten”);
* to receive the Personal Information provided by you in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and to transmit those Personal Information to another data controller (right to data portability);
* to object to the use of your Personal Information where such use is based on our legitimate interests or on public interests (right to object);
* in some cases, to restrict our use of your Personal Information (right to restriction of processing); and
* withdraw your consent at any time where our processing is based on consent (right to withdrawal of consent).
* If you are in the EEA or the UK, you also have a right to file a complaint with your local data protection authority. 

You may exercise your right to access and deletion using the buttons at the bottom of this page. Additionally, you may, at any time, send us an e-mail at [support@nuaku.net](mailto:support@nuaku.net) to exercise your above rights in accordance with the applicable legal requirements and limitations.

Please note that unless you have created an account with us, we may not have sufficient information to identify you and therefore may not be in a position to respond to your request. Additionally, in some cases in order to adequately verify your identity or your authorization to make the request, we may require you to provide additional information.

Note that some requests to delete certain personal information will require the deletion of your user account as the provision of user accounts are inextricably linked to the processing of certain personal information (e.g., your e-mail address).

### 17\. Changes to Our Privacy Notice

We may modify or revise our Privacy Notice from time to time. Although we may attempt to notify you when major changes are made to this Privacy Notice, you are expected to periodically review the most up-to-date version found at [https://www.nutaku.net/legal/tos](https://www.nutaku.com/legal/tos) so you are aware of any changes, as they are binding on you.

If we change anything in our Privacy Notice, the date of change will be reflected in the “last modified date”. You agree that you will periodically review this Privacy Notice and refresh the page when doing so. You agree to note the date of the last revision to our Privacy Notice. If the “last modified” date is unchanged from the last time you reviewed our Privacy Notice, then it is unchanged. On the other hand, if the date has changed, then there have been changes, and you agree to re-review our Privacy Notice, and you agree to the new ones. By continuing to use this Website subsequent to us making available an amended version of our Privacy Notice in a way that you can easily take notice of it, you thereby consent to such amendment.

### 18\. Enforcement; Cooperation

We regularly review our compliance with this Privacy Notice. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Notice or our treatment of Personal Information by contacting us through this Website at [support@nutaku.net](mailto:support@nutaku.net). When we receive a formal written complaint, it is our policy to contact the complaining party regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information that cannot be resolved by an individual and us.

### 19\. Notice to Law Enforcement

The following information serves as a guideline for law enforcement officials seeking disclosure of records. You may serve us a valid court order, subpoena, search warrant or equivalent legal or official administrative document by respecting the following conditions:

* The document(s) is uploaded, and all required fields have been filed out adequately on our platform for Legal Service Process located at: [https://legalservice.aylo.com/legal/datarequest](https://legalservice.aylo.com/legal/datarequest);
* The document(s) you are serving is correctly issued by a valid court of law or equivalent legal or administrative authority to us (See Websites’ footer to find our operating entity);
* The document(s) is also sent by mail at the following address: 195-197 Old Nicosia-Limassol Road, Block 1 Dali Industrial Zone, Cyprus 2540.

We reserve the right to refuse online service through our Websites, namely in cases where the above requirements are not met and require formal legal service at the above address. In such event, you will be notified. We may raise or waive any legal objection or right available, in our sole discretion.

### 20\. No Rights of Third Parties

This Privacy Notice does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any Personal Information relating to users of this Website.

### 21\. Our Policy Towards Minors

Our Website is not directed to persons under the age of 18 or the applicable age of majority in the jurisdiction from which this Website is accessed and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from minors. If you become aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us at [support@nutaku.net](mailto:support@nutaku.net). If we become aware that a minor has provided us with Personal Information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate that person’s account.

### 22\. Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice or our information-handling practices, please contact us at [privacy@nutaku.net](mailto:privacy@nutaku.net).

You may also contact us at 195-197 Old Nicosia-Limassol Road, Block 1 Dali Industrial Zone, Cyprus 2540, Phone: +357 22662 320, Fax: +357 22343 282.

Our Data Protection Officer can be contacted at the following email address: [dpo@nutaku.net](mailto:dpo@nutaku.net).

### 23\. Manage Your Private Data

Registered Users may request a copy of their personal data or request the deletion of their personal data via the links below. Please note that the below website is governed by the present Privacy Notice.

_Note: AdBlocker add-ons interfere with the Manage My Data system. Please disable them._

LanguageEnglish

* Nutaku Games

* Inclusive Adult Gaming

* Work With Us

* Support

* Discover

Language

English

© 2024 Nutaku Entertainment Ltd – All Rights Reserved.

Trademarks owned by Licensing IP International S.a.r.l. used under license by Nutaku Entertainment Ltd.

All models appearing on this website are 18 years or older. Access the required records pursuant to the [18 U.S.C. 2257 Record Keeping Requirements Compliance Statement](https://www.nutaku.net/notice/). By entering this website, you swear that you are of legal age in your area to view adult material and that you wish to view such material.

Sign Up Free & Get 200 Gold

Create your free account and check your email for a free gift!

CREATE FREE ACCOUNTLoading

 Receive Nutaku Newsletter

By signing up, you affirm you're 18+ and accept our [Terms of Use](https://www.nutaku.net/age/terms/) and [Privacy Policy](https://www.nutaku.net/age/privacy-policy/)

This site is protected by reCaptcha and the Google  
[Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and [Terms of Service](https://policies.google.com/terms)

Already have an account?

Login and play now

Login

Login and play now

LoginLoading

 Keep me signed in

Don't have an account? [**Sign up**](#)

This site is protected by reCaptcha and the Google  
[Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and [Terms of Service](https://policies.google.com/terms)

Two-Factor Authentication Enabled

Verify Code

For more information about Two-Factor Authentication please [contact support](https://www.nutaku.net/support/).

Search Nutaku for a game title, genre or tag

Oops nothing found for ""

Try again, hentai warrior! We're not going anywhere. Check your spelling or try another search

Customize Cookies

Essential Cookies

Are necessary for the website to function and cannot be switched off in our systems as they enable core website functionality

Always active

Functional Cookies

Help us to personalize and enhance your online experience on our site

Analytics Cookies

Allow us to measure & improve the performance of our site

Targeting Cookies

Allow us to provide relevant ads & content based on your browsing activity

Accept All Cookies Accept Only Essential Cookies Save And Apply
